Breya|"Hey Emilia, where have you been? We were supposed to meet an hour ago"|0|L
Emilia|"I found an old sentinel that was exposed after last night’s rain."|1|R
Emilia|"I’ve been trying to pry some parts off of it, but it was buried pretty deep."|1|R
Breya|"Couldn’t you have just used magic to get it out?"|0|L
Emilia|"Yeah, but I didn’t want to damage it."|1|R
Breya|"Well, Good thing I brought my drill today!"|0|L
Breya|"The battery is shot though, so I’ll have to charge it pretty often."|0|L
Emilia|"Let’s hurry! I think it’s a really good find, and I don’t want anybody else to claim it."|1|R
Breya|"Yes! Finally got the first piece off!"|0|L
Emilia|"I told you they were stuck on tight. I wonder why the batteries are never in these."|1|R
Breya|"Wait, I think there’s someone coming."|0|L
Emilia|"Probably another scavenger."|1|R
Breya|"Hey! We found the site first! This is our claim, back off!"|0|L
Emilia|"Huh, it’s a district soldier. Why’s he all the way out here?"|1|R
Soldier|"Which one of you is Emilia?"|2|C
Breya|"What’s a district soldier doing so far from the city?"|0|L
Soldier|"I have orders to escort her to the city for assessment."|2|C
Emilia|"Mages have been going missing lately, I’d rather not."|1|R
Soldier|"You don’t have a choice. You’re under arrest."|2|C
|"Press ENTER to Continue.."|0|L